Harshali Harjani

Email: harshi.harjani@gmail.com

Mobile: +91-8390486870

I'm a Salesforce Consultant with 6+ years of experience in Salesforce.com as a Salesforce Administrator, Functional Consultant, Instructor, Business Analyst, QA. During my tenure, I have been involved in various Salesforce life-cycle implementations for companies like Banking, Health-care, Telecom, Education, etc. and pursue skills in analyzing Business and Functional requirement through analysis, design, development, configuration, QA and implementation via different Salesforce modules.

I possess better understanding on the below:

- SFDC CRM Sales and Service Cloud Application capabilities and constraints
- SOQL, and the Salesforce security model
- Extensive experience in workflows, role model, hierarchy, profiles and permission sets, Communities, Reports and dashboards, Live-agent functionality and forecast.
- Data migration tool like Dataloader

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS:

Education	College/School	University/Board	Year of Passing	Marks
MBA - IT	Bharati Vidyapeeth School of Distance Learning	Bharati Vidyapeeth Deemed University	2016	63.92%
B.S.C(Computer Science)	Govt. Holkar Science College	DAVV University	2012	75.8%
H.S.C	St. Mary's Convent Senior Secondary School	CBSE Board	2009	78%
S.S.C	St. Mary's Convent Senior Secondary School	CBSE Board	2007	80.6%

- Salesforce certified Administrator (ADM 201).
- Salesforce certified Advanced Administrator (ADM 211).
- Force.com certified Developer (DEV 401).
- Salesforce certified Platform App builder.
- Salesforce certified Platform Developer I

TOOLS:

Data Loader, Eclipse (Elementary knowledge), ANT tool, Workbench, Force.com IDE within Eclipse, JIRA

PROFESSIONAL STRENGTH:

- Self-Motivated and goal oriented.
- Detail oriented and possess strong analytical skill.
- Ability to train and manage subordinates.
- Positive attitude.
- Highly organized individual, adept at multitasking, ability to assume responsibility.

ACHIEVEMENTS:

• Promoted as Subject Matter Expert in March'16

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

> From 10th August 2017 – Till Date at Accenture

Profile: Functional Consultant/Business Analyst

Client: Goldman Sach

Responsibilities:

- Assisted in developing Project Scope, Business Requirements and Functional Requirements with internal team and clients.
- Basic understanding of Customization (Apex controllers, Apex Classes, Apex Triggers, VisualForce Pages and SOQL Queries).
- Developed simple Visualforce Pages and Triggers as per Requirements.
- Worked on Deployments using Changesets, Eclipse and ANT.
- Worked on Deployments for project at the end of each development cycle to ensure components were intact.
- Created and Worked on Sites and Communities for users for project needs.
- Good understanding of Sales and Service process also worked on Sales Cloud and Service Console.
- Worked on Service Cloud for Case Management for Web-to-case and Email-to-case.

- Configured SFDC workflow rules, Approval process, Process Builders.
- To manage data i.e. to import, delete, update data using Data Loader.
- Worked on Configuring a complete Sandbox and Maintaining it. Performed Pre&Post sandbox refresh steps.
- Involved in manual testing for projects and bug fixing.
- Configured Salesforce for Outlook from scratch ensuring the connection worked and items synced as required.
- Worked on shield implementation for encrypting the data in Salesforce.
- Assisted in encryption/ decryption of data and other components involved via third party apps like Ciphercloud.

Client: Xactly Corporation

Responsibilities:

- Working on Xactly CRM a Compensation tool that aids various organizations in setting payouts for their payees
 every month, calculate bonuses if applicable quarterly or yearly or otherwise put the payout on hold if certain
 criteria isn't met. This is an automation tool assisting HR's in their field of work, in meeting the right values
 successfully and error-free.
- Setting up client meets for business understanding and requirement gathering.
- Generating functional document for reference between the two involved parties.
- Configuring the Xactly Incent to evaluate credits and commissions appropriately, thereby resulting in payouts for the employees in an organization.
- Involved in end-to-end development of the plan ensuring all the test cases are covered and the data sets are accurate.
- Generating reports that are easy to understand from a Managerial perspective.
- Representation of the components graphically for better acknowledgement.
- Involved in manual testing of the plans along with migration of the data into production once the design is agreed upon.

> From 9th July 2014 – 28th July 2016 at Cognizant Technology Services

Profile: Salesforce CRM Administrator

Client: Salesforce

Responsibilities:

- To administer, develop and manage the Salesforce CRM application.
- To create fields, page layouts, custom objects and managing them.
- To create workflow rules, assignment rules, escalation rules, duplicate rules based on user's requirement.
- To create logical formula fields with proper functions to meet user's requirement.
- To create community users and manage their profiles.
- To create profiles, permission set wherever necessary.
- To create criteria based and user base sharing rule wherever necessary.
- To manage forecasts and quotas.
- To create reports and dashboards based on the needs.
- To troubleshoot problems wherever necessary.

- To develop processes and flows where the requirement couldn't be achieved using the point and click functionality.
- To develop Triggers, Classes and Pages to override the standard look and feel as well as to automate the process
- To manage data i.e. to import, delete, update data using Data Loader.

From August 2012 – June 2014 at IBM

Profile: CRM Practitioner (Salesforce Administration)

<u>Client – Virgin Airways and Genband:</u>

Responsibilities:

- To administer, develop and manage the Salesforce CRM application for internal users.
- To create fields, page layouts, custom objects and managing them.
- To create workflow rules, assignment rules, escalation rules based on user's requirement.
- To create logical formula fields with proper functions to meet user's requirement.
- To create profiles, permission set wherever necessary.
- To create criteria based and user base sharing rule wherever necessary.
- To manage forecasts and quotas.
- To create reports and dashboards based on the needs.
- To troubleshoot problems wherever necessary.

PERSONAL INFORMATION:

Date of Birth: 30th October 1991

Sex: Female

Marital Status: Single

Languages: English, Hindi, Sindhi

Hobbies: Basketball, Reading Books and listening to music

Permanent Address: Pune, India

I hereby declare that the above-mentioned information given is true to the best of my knowledge.

Place: PUNE HARSHALI HARJANI